alden-tan.com 2015-12-11

# Privacy Policy - Alden-tan.com

Your privacy [order research paper cheap](http://alden-tan.com/order-research-paper-cheap/ "order research paper cheap") is very important to me. Accordingly, I have created this Policy in order for you to understand how I collect, use, communicate and [education homework help](http://www.randomframe.org/pdr-education-homework-help/ "education homework help") disclose and make use of personal information. The following [who to write a research paper](http://alden-tan.com/do-my-homework-write-my-papers/) outlines my privacy policy.

\- Before or at the point of collecting personal information, I will identify the purposes for information is being collected.

\- Most often, the personal information comes in the form of NAME and EMAIL only.

\- Even in the <http://www.medicinareprodutiva.org/professional-essay-writers/> event that you buy my products, your name and email is only provided to me. Your credit card information will never [literature research paper](http://alden-tan.com/literature-research-paper/ "literature research paper") be disclosed to me.

\- I will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless I obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.

\- I’ll only retain personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.

\- I will only collect personal information by lawful and fair means only.

- Personal data should be [essay writing for internet](http://alden-tan.com/essay-writing-for-internet/ "essay writing for internet") relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.

\- I will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.

\- I will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.

\- I am committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
